applications are open to be on the
scientific Advisory Board the Sab for
the active inference Institute in 2024
this is a volunteer position that is
designed to be valuable meaningful and
time efficient for Sab members as well
as the Institute Sab members with
different skills and perspectives
including a wide range of familiarity
with active inference engage with the
active inference ecosystem in multiple
ways including joining optional monthly
Sab discussion sessions to give insights
and connect with other sabb members Sab
members support The Institute by making
connections and collaborating on
philanthropic and Grant programs Sab
members participate directly in ongoing
Institute activities and also propose or
lead education or research projects of
their own like Chris fields and the
physics as information processing course
in 2023 and also we're always looking to
Sab members to lead Alternative forms of
Engagement so if there's something
that's interested interesting to you
then we're excited to maybe hear about
it see our website active inference
org scientific Advisory Board and on
this page you'll see a little bit more
information about the Sab you'll see our
20123 and
2022 cohorts and this 2024 will be the
third cohort of the sa and you can click
on this link on the site to apply
directly
please submit your application for 2024
sa before December 15th 2023 and let us
know wherever you're seeing this video
or by email at blanket active inference
Institute if you have any questions
thank you
bye